<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dr. İlker Ali ÖZKAN</title>
    <link>http://www.ilkeraliozkan.com.tr/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dr. İlker Ali ÖZKAN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>tr-tr</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.ilkeraliozkan.com.tr/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic: the website designer for Hugo</title>
      <link>http://www.ilkeraliozkan.com.tr/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ilkeraliozkan.com.tr/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Academic is a framework to help you create a beautiful website quickly. Perfect for personal sites, blogs, or business/project sites. Check out the latest demo of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes. Then head on over to the Quick Start guide or take a look at the Release Notes.

Key features:
 Easily manage various content including homepage, blog posts, publications, talks, and projects Extensible via color themes and widgets/plugins Write in Markdown for easy formatting and code highlighting, with LaTeX for mathematical expressions Social/academic network linking, Google Analytics, and Disqus comments Responsive and mobile friendly Simple and refreshing one page design Multilingual and easy to customize  Color Themes Academic is available in different color themes and font themes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Publications</title>
      <link>http://www.ilkeraliozkan.com.tr/post/my_publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ilkeraliozkan.com.tr/post/my_publications/</guid>
      <description>A -Uluslararası Çalışmalar 
&amp;nbsp;
A-1:SCI, SCI-expanded, SSCI, AHCI’de yer alan ve Impact faktörü 1.0 ve üzeri olan uluslar arası dergilerde yayımlanan araştırma makaleleri
&amp;nbsp;
1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Ilker Ali OZKAN, Murat KOKLU, Ibrahim Unal SERT, (2018), Diagnosisof Urinary Tract Infection based on Artificial Intelligence Methods, ComputerMethods and Programs in Biomedicine, vol:166, pp. 51-59, doi: 10.1016/j.cmpb.2018.10.007
2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Ilker Ali OZKAN, Saadetdin HERDEM, Ismail SARITAS, (2017), FPGA-based self-organizing fuzzy controller for electromagnetic filter, NeuralComputing and Applications (NCAA),28 (9), pp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>